████████╗██╗ ██████╗██╗  ██╗███████╗████████╗    ████████╗ ██████╗     ██████╗ ██╗██████╗ ███████╗
╚══██╔══╝██║██╔════╝██║ ██╔╝██╔════╝╚══██╔══╝    ╚══██╔══╝██╔═══██╗    ██╔══██╗██║██╔══██╗██╔════╝
   ██║   ██║██║     █████╔╝ █████╗     ██║          ██║   ██║   ██║    ██████╔╝██║██║  ██║█████╗  
   ██║   ██║██║     ██╔═██╗ ██╔══╝     ██║          ██║   ██║   ██║    ██╔══██╗██║██║  ██║██╔══╝  
   ██║   ██║╚██████╗██║  ██╗███████╗   ██║          ██║   ╚██████╔╝    ██║  ██║██║██████╔╝███████╗
   ╚═╝   ╚═╝ ╚═════╝╚═╝  ╚═╝╚══════╝   ╚═╝          ╚═╝    ╚═════╝     ╚═╝  ╚═╝╚═╝╚═════╝ ╚══════╝
                                                                                                  
                 ██████╗ ███████╗██████╗ ███╗   ███╗ █████╗ ███╗   ██╗██╗   ██╗                   
                ██╔════╝ ██╔════╝██╔══██╗████╗ ████║██╔══██╗████╗  ██║╚██╗ ██╔╝                   
                ██║  ███╗█████╗  ██████╔╝██╔████╔██║███████║██╔██╗ ██║ ╚████╔╝                    
                ██║   ██║██╔══╝  ██╔══██╗██║╚██╔╝██║██╔══██║██║╚██╗██║  ╚██╔╝                     
                ╚██████╔╝███████╗██║  ██║██║ ╚═╝ ██║██║  ██║██║ ╚████║   ██║                      
                 ╚═════╝ ╚══════╝╚═╝  ╚═╝╚═╝     ╚═╝╚═╝  ╚═╝╚═╝  ╚═══╝   ╚═╝                      
                                                                                                  
By - Michael LeRoy, Cassandra Summo, Grace Slavin, Luis Villa, Zachary Goodsell

Step 1 - Installation
For this step you will need to open this project in Netbeans. To do so you open netbean and go to the open projects button.
Next to navigate to this directory the game is in and select open. Then you click the green run arrow at the top of the page
to start the game.

Step 2 - Selecting Game
When the game opens you can select 2-5 player then select start new game.

Step 3 - Playing the Game - Destination Cards
When selecting destination tickets, after selecting the minimum ammount of
cards for that turn you can click done or continue slecting cards. If you
select all four card the game will click done for you. When you hover over
the selected cards two transparent arrows appear over the desination cities.

Step 4 - Playing the Game - Train cards
When getting train cards you can do one of the following moves -
-Take one face up rainbow locomotive
-Take 2 face up non-locomative cards
-Take 2 face down cards
-Take 1 face up non-locomative card and one face down card

Step 5 - Playing the Game - Selecting Routes
Once you have enough cards to buy a path you can right click on cards to select them
and left click on cards to deselect them. Once enough cards are selected you can click
on the path to buy it.

Step 6 - Playing the Game - Meeples
When you buy a route, you get your choice of meeples from the two connecting. The
avalible meeples are show in the bottom right corner. Because these meeples are mixed
together, in order to see the meeples of each city you have to hover over the city and
the meeple count and types appear in the top right.

Step 7 - Playing the Game - End of Game
The last round starts when a player has less then 3 trains left to play. After this 
everyone has one final turn, including that player. After the game is over a results
screen appears.
